blinkforhome.com 2017-12-24

# Privacy Policy | Blink

Blink for Home, Immedia Semiconductor and our affiliates (together “Blink,” “we” or “us”) are committed to protecting the privacy of our users’ Personal Information. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use, retain, disclose, process and transfer Personal Information. This Privacy Policy applies to all personal information we collect, regardless of whether the information is collected when you use the [www.immediasemi.com](http://immediasemi.com/) website or the www.blinkforhome.com website; (the“Sites”), through the Blink product or other equipment you purchase from Blink (“Equipment”), through our downloadable software such as the Blink mobile application (“Software”), or in connection with our home security and automation service (the “Home Service”). This policy covers information we collect online and offline.

Any Personally Identifiable Information or Personal Data (“Personal Information”) collected by the Sites, the Equipment, the Software or the Home Service shall be used only in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy. Personal Information is information about you that is personally identifying, such as your name, email address, postal address, or telephone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. Personal Information may also include a person’s voice and image when recorded by the Equipment, Software or Home Service. The definition of Personal Information depends on your physical location and may include other types of information. Only the legal definition that applies to your physical location will apply to you under this Privacy Policy.

**Agreement**

**By accessing the Sites or Software, purchasing Equipment, using the Home Service, emailing us, or applying for a job, you accept and hereby expressly consent to our collection, use, retention, processing, disclosure and transfer, including international disclosure and transfer, of your Personal Information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. You also expressly consent and opt in to receive promotional emails from Blink and understand that you may opt out by clicking “unsubscribe” on the emails you receive from us.**

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page and update the Privacy Policy modification date. Please check back regularly to review any changes to this Privacy Policy and each time your submit Personal Information to us. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy or any changes to it, you should not use or access the Sites, Equipment, Software or Home Services. This policy was last modified on October 12, 2016.

**Information Collection and Use; Choice and Consent**

You can browse the Sites and download some content such as our press kit without providing any Personal Information, although your IP address will be collected. Use of other features on the Sites require you to provide Personal Information, as described below.

_blinkforhome.com  
_ When you contact us through the Contact Us button on www.blinkforhome.com, we collect your email address, full name and Blink username so we can respond to your request. When you subscribe to our newsletter and email updates, we collect your email address and first and last name so we can provide you with the requested information.

When you make a purchase on the Site, you will be asked to provide your email address, first and last name, shipping address, zip code or postal code, and your billing information including your credit card number and its expiration date and security code. When you make a purchase through the Site, this information is collected by our third party payment processor and is not collected by us. Once your order is fulfilled and shipped, our third party payment processor provides us with your name, email address, phone number, postal address, customer ID and the last four digits of your credit card number. Your Personal Information will be used to process and fulfill your order, provide the requested services, validate, create and monitor your account and user profile, and provide you with product information and updates.

If you apply for a job with us through the Site, you must register and provide your email address, password, first and last name, address, zip code and phone number. You must also provide a resume or C.V. We collect this information in order to assess your qualifications for a job with us and to contact you for more information if we deem necessary. We retain your information until the job you applied for is filled.

_Software  
_ When you use or access the Software, we collect your name, phone number, email address, encrypted password, IP address, geographic location and encrypted video clips. We also collect non-personal information including environmental data (temperature and humidity) from your Blink camera. We collect this information in order to provide you with your video and audio clips, to validate, create and monitor your account and user profile, to send you email and text message alerts, and to allow us and our third party service providers to host and store your encrypted video clips as part of the Home Service.

The Software enables users to view and download video and audio clips from their Blink camera. Users may download and save video and audio clips to onboard storage, or they may be stored in our secure cloud. All video and audio clips are encrypted during transmission. Once you download or store an audio or video clip on your own device, we no longer have control over the processing or disclosure of the audio or video clip, and this Privacy Policy will not apply to your personal collection, processing or disclosure of audio or video clips.

_Promotional Emails  
_ If you submit an email address to us for any reason, we will add you to our email marketing list and we will send you promotional emails. You may unsubscribe by clicking “unsubscribe” at the bottom of the emails you receive.

It is always your choice whether or not to provide us with Personal Information. If you do provide Personal Information to the Sites, you are giving your voluntary and express consent to the collection, use, processing, retention, transfer and disclosure, including international transfer and disclosure, of your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you choose not to provide the requested information you may not be able to access certain features or functions of the Sites and you will not be able to purchase Software, Equipment or our Home Service. You may access, change, modify or delete your information, at any time, as described below.

You may opt out from receipt of our emails by clicking “unsubscribe” at the bottom of the emails you receive from us. You have the right to object to the use of your Personal Information for direct marketing purposes by email, on a going forward basis, by emailing us at info@blinkforhome.com. We will respond to your objection in accordance with the law that applies to you.

You may revoke your consent, and/or object to or block processing of your Personal Information by emailing a request to us at info@blinkforhome.com.We will respond to your request in accordance with the law that applies to you. Your Personal Information which we processed prior to your request may not be deleted from our Sites system records but will be blocked from further processing without your permission. A request to revoke consent or block processing of your Personal Information may not apply to information collected by cookies or used internally to recognize you and/or facilitate your visits to the Sites, or to information we may keep to comply with legal requirements.

We will retain your Personal Information as long as necessary to facilitate the use of our products or services. When you cancel your subscription to the Service, we will delete your Personal Information within a reasonable time afterwards

**Do We Use Cookies or other Tracking Technologies?**

We use cookies. Cookies are small files that a website or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive or to the memory of your mobile device through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the websites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Service.

We also use other technologies such as clear gifs, pixel tags, and scanning navigational data to collect anonymous information about our users in order to help us deliver better service and user experience. Examples of anonymous information include the Sites you were on before coming to our Site, IP addresses (in some cases), or areas of the Sites being clicked on most frequently.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about traffic and interaction with the Sites and services so that we can offer better Site and service experiences and tools in the future.

Most Web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone or by contacting customer service.

_Google Analytics  
_ The Web Site uses Google Analytics. For more information about Google analytic cookies, please see Google’s help pages and privacy policy:

[https://developers.google.com/analytics/resources/concepts/gaConceptsCookies](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage)

Google have developed the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on for the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, dc.js). If you want to opt out of Google Analytics, you can download and install the add-on for your web browser [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en).

For more information on our cookies, please see our Cookie Statement

**Protection of Your Information**

We will take appropriate physical, technical and organizational measures to protect Personal Information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers database, only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and who are required to keep the information confidential.

No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

We will retain Personal Information we process for as long as needed to provide the Services. We will retain and use this Personal Information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements, and to resolve any issues relating to fraud or other cyber threats.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

We share your Personal Information with our third party vendors who assist us and enable us to provide the Sites and services. We disclose your encrypted video clips to our third party service providers in order to provide you with video hosting services. We will not make your video clips publicly available. We disclose your email address to third parties for direct marketing purposes. In addition, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to Google Analytics or other third party analytics services.

We also may transfer any and all information that we collect about you to third parties in the event of any merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our assets or stock (including without limitation in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings). You will be notified in advance of any rights you may have to block or object to this transfer of your information.

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our Site policies, or protect our or other’s rights, property, or safety, or to assist with any online fraud or cyber threats. Because our servers, which store your information, are located in the U.S.A., your information may be available to U.S. government entities or agencies under a lawful court order in the U.S.

By accessing our Site or any of the Services, you provide your express consent to our disclosure of your Personal Information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy.

**Third Party Sites and Links; Payment Processors**

Our Site may contain links to other websites that are independent, are not owned or operated by us, are not covered by this Privacy Policy and which may incorporate third party information. For example, when you purchase Equipment, your Personal Data and payment information will be collected and processed by our third party payment processor. Currently, we use [Shopify.com](http://shopify.com/) and [Amazon.com](http://amazon.com/) to process payments. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies that apply to the information they collect from you. If you access other sites using the links provided, the operators of these sites may collect information from you, which will be used by them in accordance with their privacy policy, which may differ from ours. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of other websites, even if they are linked to our Site.

**Social Media Features**

Our Site includes features from social media websites such as the Facebook Like button and features on Twitter, LinkedIn and Google+ and others that run on our Site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these features. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy and other policies of the companies providing them. Please be sure to read the privacy policies of social media websites before you provide or post any personally identifiable information or Personal Data.

**Your California Privacy Rights; California Do Not Track Disclosures**

If you are a California resident, California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits you to request information regarding the disclosure of your personal information by us or our subsidiaries to a third party for the third party’s direct marketing purposes. Since we do not make such disclosures, we are exempt from these reporting requirements. In addition, we currently do not honor Do Not Track signals.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), as we do not knowingly collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. The Site is a business-to-business Site directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**International or Cross-Border Transfer of Your Personal Information and Your Express Agreement**

Given that the Internet operates in a global environment and that transfer of your data is necessary to enable you to use the features and services on the Site, to provide updates, and to respond to your inquiries, using the Internet to collect and process Personal Information necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international, or cross-border, basis. By signing up for or using the Services, and/or by communicating with us by email, you acknowledge and expressly consent to our processing and disclosure of your Personal Information in this way. The Personal Information of users who are located in Germany will be stored on our server in Frankfurt, Germany. We also process Personal Information for customer support purposes in Ireland and the U.S. The Personal Information of users who are located in the U.K. or other locations outside the U.S. (excluding Germany) will be transferred outside of each eligible country to the United States where our servers are located and where it will be processed and stored on servers in the U.S. The U.S. has not been recognized as providing an adequate level of protection according to European Union (EU) data protection requirements, but we will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that users’ Personal Information is treated securely in respect of such transfer and as described in this Privacy Policy. **By using the Site and by providing information to the Site, you expressly agree to such transfer, processing, storage and disclosure in countries outside the EU.**

You may access, review, change, update or delete your Personal Information, request information about our collection, use and disclosure of such information, and request information on our policies and practices relating to disclosure of information to our service providers, by contacting us at [info@blinkforhome.com](mailto:info@blink.com). We will respond to these requests in accordance with the laws that apply to you. You can help us maintain the accuracy of your information by promptly notifying us of any changes to your information.

**Contact Us About Complaints, Questions or Notices relating to this Privacy Policy**

We are committed to resolving complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your Personal Information. If you believe your privacy rights have been violated or you disagree with any action Media Links has taken with regard to your Personal Information you may file a complaint with us by emailing us at [info@blinkforhome.com](mailto:info@blink.com). Users with complaints about their privacy or this Privacy Policy should submit their complaint in writing with as much information as possible. Complaints will be acknowledged within a reasonable period of time, consistent with applicable law.

You may contact us at:

**Privacy Officer  
** Immedia  
100 Burtt Road, Suite 100  
Andover, Massachusetts, USA, 01810  
Phone: 781-915-1920  

**Terms of Service  
** Please also visit our Terms of Service section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our Sites.

_Updated: October 26, 2016_
